CEI gathers some types of information from visitors to our websites, chiefly “CEI.org”.  Below is more information on what data CEI collects and what we do with it.

**Information Collected By CEI.org**  
CEI.org collects two types of information from users: 1) personal data and 2) aggregated data, such as information about traffic patterns on CEI.org.

**Personal Data**  
Personal information, such as zip code, email address, or demographic information, can only be collected if a visitor voluntarily chooses to fill out a form and supply CEI with this information.

**Aggregated Data**  
Aggregated information, such as which pages users visit, is collected through various means. Two such ways are through cookies, a small file which your web browser downloads along with all of the other continent of CEI.org, and IP addresses, a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web. Web servers, the computers that “serve up” Web pages, automatically identify your computer by its IP address. When you view a page from CEI.org, our servers log your IP address. CEI.org does not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, so although your session will be logged, it will remain anonymous to us. CEI.org collects IP addresses and information from cookies for the purposes of improving the quality of the site for visitors.

**Use of Information Collected by CEI.org**  
CEI.org uses the information we collect to improve the content and layout of the site and, if requested, to provide information services by email to the user. CEI.org does not provide any of the information it collects with third parties.

**Links to Other Sites**  
Note that CEI.org contains links to sites other than itself, and that those sites may not follow the same privacy policies as CEI.org.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**  
CEI reserves the right to change its privacy policy and such changes will be noted in a revised privacy policy statement.

**How to Contact Us about Our Privacy Policy**  
Please send any privacy policy questions to [\[email protected\]](https://cei.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

_The privacy policy was last revised and updated on March 1, 2017._
